What are you up to?
Weren't you going to take Mrs. Lin's case?
Why did you suddenly change your mind
and go look for Liang Zidong?
Where are we even driving to?
Just follow the address on the navigation for now.
Let me ask you something.
Doesn't Rujie occasionally
get one of those crucial cases
that can directly impact
the firm's growth for the next 3-5 years?
I haven't been here long myself.
How would I know all that?
But I asked around.
This Liang Zidong case
is probably exactly what you mean.
So that means
whoever finds Liang Zidong
will get to take this case,
and all the firm's future resources
will be focused on them, right?
Right.
And for a young lawyer,
whoever manages to take this case
can practically transform their career.
But so far,
there's been zero progress.
He's very likely to show up at a hospital.
A hospital?
Why?
Earlier, when I was looking at
the video evidence Mrs. Lin gave me,
I noticed that
Liang Zidong also appeared in the video.
And after I zoomed in on the footage,
guess what I saw?
Liang Zidong injecting himself with insulin.
Hello.
Are you Liang Zidong's wife?
I'm Ding Ning from Rujie Law Firm.
The thing is,
regarding your husband's case,
we have a few questions.
Would you mind helping us out?
Does your husband regularly take insulin?
How often does he get his medication?
Do you mind telling me?
What brand is it?
And what's the dosage?
His insulin is a foreign brand.
I checked every hospital and pharmacy,
and found that only this hospital
has this brand of insulin.
Plus, per his medical insurance records,
counting back from his last refill,
his medication is almost out.
Which means,
no matter where Liang Zidong is kept,
for his health,
they will have to bring Liang Zidong
here to buy insulin.
Then we just have to lie in wait.
If we stake out the hospital for two days,
we might just catch him.
How did you find that out?
Just had to ask the medicine scalpers.
Impressive, Ding Ning.
Let's see if we can catch him then.
I'll go talk to the Security Office soon
to pull two days of surveillance footage.
What are these two kids doing?
Jumping on a trampoline.
What?
A trampoline?
Awu is amazing at the trampoline!
You've made a lot of new friends, right?
Awu...
Grandpa has to go out. I'll be back later.
Can you take care of yourself?
Okay.
All right.
I'll bring you some treats later, okay?
Be good.
You're here.
Want to go for a walk?
Careful, don't scratch it.
Here we go.
My dad built all these buildings here too.
Your dad is amazing.
Let's go. I'll show you around.
Close the door.
Easy, easy.
What do you think this family does?
Don't take other people's things.
Think they were just lying here like this?
Someone's coming.
Let's go!
Why isn't he talking?
He can't speak.
And he can't stand up either.
Do you know him?
No, I don't.
I have someone like this at home too.
Let's take him out to play.
Be careful.
Don't drop it.
Let's go back.
Otherwise, his family will worry.
Why do all these buildings look the same?
I don't think it's this one.
It must be that one.
Grandpa, do you remember your home?
It's over. We can't find his home.
This will help grandpa find his home.
Definitely.
It's way better than us searching blindly.
Ready.
Three, two, one.
Go!
Wait a minute.
Ready. Three, two, one.
Go.
Stop looking. Let's go.
Hurry up.
Hurry, hurry!
Sir, why are you here all alone?
Where is your family?
Grandpa, who brought you here?
Why are you back so late too?
What's wrong?
A few days ago,
someone passed away.
I had to send him for cremation.
These are his gold tooth and stones.
See how you want to handle them.
So it turns out,
a person can eventually turn into ashes,
and then they just
put it in a little box.
The strange thing is,
I really didn't feel anything.
Was that person your friend?
Not really.
But compared to so-called friends,
we were a bit more complicated.
You've been writing to me all these years.
Why?
Because I hate you.
I didn't want you to move on so easily.
Think you're the only one in prison?
I've been in one too.
Then I actually felt relieved.
I was wondering why I'd feel relieved.
Maybe I'm just afraid that
now that he's free,
everything between us
just went away with him.
The once-unforgettable memories
are fading away bit by bit.
Afraid of what?
I don't know.
What about you?
Why are you up so late?
Endless things to do.
Then go back to your room and sleep.
Also helping Zhao Yijie find Liang Zidong?
The other day when we had dumplings,
I noticed the paper under our plates
had the Fuxia Group logo on it.
And so did the paper you just threw away.
May I speak frankly?
Go ahead.
I just wanted to say,
Zhao Yijie adopted Yang A'wu,
but it's like you adopted him.
The kid is here with you most of the time.
Even with Rujie's affairs,
he asks for your help day and night.
I know it's not my place to say this,
but isn't he taking a mile
when you give him an inch?
Besides, the kid is going to grow up.
What if one day, when the time comes,
Zhao Yijie, for Yang's sake...
Ding Ning, what if...
Just hypothetically, what if
something happens to Zhao Yijie and me,
would you adopt Yang A'wu?
Hello, Zhou Hao.
I found them. Come quickly.
What's the situation?
They're right inside.
Which room is Liang Zidong in?
It's all up to you now.
I'll back you up from out here.
Alright.
Keep an eye on your phone.
Okay.
Just a second.
The Deposit will go back to your account.
Thank you.
Hello.
Hello. Do you have any rooms available?
Yes, we do.
Need a Standard room or a Deluxe room?
So, here's the thing.
Our company is having a team building.
We're thinking of next week,
and we'll probably need 7 or 8 rooms.
And, well...
our boss is a little superstitious.
He wants the sixth floor.
For good luck, you know.
I'm sorry.
We've already leased out the 6th floor.
There are no vacant rooms at the moment.
I see.
How about this?
We still have rooms on the fifth floor.
The layout is identical to the 6th floor.
Let me show you.
The fifth floor...
That works too.
Okay, please wait a moment.
Okay.
This way.
Hello, I'd like a room.
I have a reservation.
Okay, please wait a moment then.
Alright, how about I head up first?
Okay.
Hello.
Zhou Hao,
Liang Zidong is in 601.
Call Zhao Yijie right now.
Tell him to hurry over.
Bye.
What are you doing?
I'm Ding Ning, Liang Zidong's legal counsel.
During his residential surveillance,
I invoke the Right to meet with client.
If within three minutes,
I don't message my partner downstairs,
he will be certain
you're stopping me from seeing Mr. Liang.
Then my partner will immediately
send a Complaint letter to the Bureau of Justice.
That way, even if you
get any evidence out of him in that room,
I can use this to petition the court
for the Exclusionary rule.
Making your interrogation useless.
You're a lawyer just because you say so?
The Representation Agreement and paperwork
are in my phone.
Your inefficiency leaves you with
only one minute left to hesitate.
Oops, how careless.
The phone screen is completely shattered.
Guess we can't verify your identity now.
That's fine. I'm meticulous.
Should we notify the Captain?
Meeting my client alone is my right.
You have no right to sit in.
Mr. Liang.
I am your legal counsel, Ding Ning.
Great. They finally sent me a lawyer.
Hello, hello.
Well...
There are police outside.
Did they give you a hard time?
Come, have a seat.
I'm fine.
The whole law firm was looking for you.
I never expected
this place to be so close to Rujie.
You're from Rujie?
Zhao Yijie sent you?
Yes. You'll be able to go home soon
and reunite with your family.
Go home?
My wife. My child.
I didn't say anything!
I swear I'll take the fall for everything.
Tell Zhao Yijie not to touch my family.
About the base,
I didn't say anything.
I didn't say a word.
The base?
What base?
You've been set up by Zhao Yijie.
Zhao Yijie's specialty is a Cunning escape.
I, the CFO,
am the scapegoat for Fuxia Group.
You are my lawyer now.
You'll eventually be his scapegoat too.
From the moment you walked in here,
whether I told you the truth or not,
you can't wash your hands of this now.
Now we must work together.
Saving me means saving yourself.
Do you understand?
I'm waiting for you to calm down.
You don't understand the situation at all!
Fuxia Group and Rujie Law Firm
are just a Front for those people.
Those people?
Mr. Liang.
Everything you are saying right now
is most likely
a stress response from being frightened.
It cannot be used as evidence
and has no legal effect whatsoever.
The reason I'm still here
is just to wait for you to calm down.
If you want to talk now,
I'm just listening.
But I absolutely won't discuss it.
Fine. Then listen to me.
There's only one way now
for both of us to get out of this safely.
You need to go somewhere.
Where?
I just mentioned it.
The base.
The Fraudulent Litigation Base.
Fraudulent litigation
You mean
Zhao Yijie wants you to use this
Fraudulent Litigation Base
to do some work for Fuxia Group.
Illegal Asset transfers.
Professionally, you're my lawyer.
You need to help me
gain leverage with the Prosecutor's Office
and help me get a sentence reduction.
Personally, you're already involved.
If you don't have
leverage that makes Zhao Yijie fear you,
you'll end up worse off than me.
I just wanted to remind you
you don't have to push yourself so hard.
You can always say no.
Of course, I can also tell
that you really care about Awu.
Awu relies on you a lot, too.
Or you could say Awu's arrival
made your once ordinary life
suddenly so much richer.
But
his current legal guardian
is Zhao Yijie, after all.
What are you doing?
We suspect that
you're helping Liang conceal illegal gains.
Come with us to Assist with investigation.
Move.
Let me go!
You need a Detention warrant to take me!
What do you think you're doing?
No, no, no! I'll do it, I'll do it.
Unlock them.
The keys! Keys!
Unlock them! Unlock them!
You must Summon for questioning legally.
You can't restrict her personal freedom.
You broke protocol.
Let's go.
It was a misunderstanding, miss.
Sorry for the rough treatment.
Hold on.
Let me see.
Who hurt Lawyer Ding from Rujie Law Firm?
Lawyer Zhao, here's the situation.
Here's the situation, Lawyer Zhao.
Who was it?
Lawyer Zhao.
I'm the case handler for this case.
What happens under my watch is on me.
I'll apologize, alright?
I'll make him apologize.
Right now.
Stop with the stubbornness.
Show some remorse.
I'm sorry.
I'll treat you some other time.
I had Zhou Hao head back first.
Old Liang's case is yours now.
I wasn't trying to...
Say no more.
Get some rest today.
Tomorrow afternoon,
Xu Ruqing and I will wait at the law firm.
Get in.
I'll take you home.
I asked you for just one thing.
Just one.
Keep an eye on Ding Ning.
Keep her out of Fuxia Group's plans.
And what did you promise me?
Now she's busy all day
with a Fuxia Group programmer's DUI case.
It's such a trivial case.
Who would ever connect it
to Liang Zidong's disappearance?
What are you panicking for?
If Yu Songfan finds out about Ding Ning...
Then let them find out.
Yu Songfan's fate
is already sealed now.
Adding Ding Ning to the mix,
I don't think it matters.
How far are Ma Tingting and the others?
To be honest,
I don't know.
Right now,
dozens, even hundreds of eyes
are watching us.
We can't use our old methods anymore.
I know that too.
I don't know if I should say this.
How did you get like this?
In the past,
let alone one Ding Ning,
a dozen Ding Nings or twenty Yu Songfans
wouldn't make you bat an eye.
We'd just do it for Mr. Bi.
I'll leave it at that.
But I really hope
you don't let a child
and your so-called
little game of playing house
make you go completely soft.
Alright?
What's wrong?
They're making me go to school.
Are we still going out to play then?
How about
I take you to another home?
How come you have two homes?
That's nothing.
I even have a home in the mountains.
This is your place too.
It's so grand.
Compared to the houses my dad built,
it's way more impressive.
Want some water?
Your fridge is so big.
Too bad there's no ice cream.
I'm jealous.
What is this?
It's open.
Gold and gemstones.
Let's each take one.
Is that okay?
It's fine.
These belong to your family.
You take the gold, I'll take the gemstone.
What did you say?
Say that again.
I'd say the same thing ten more times.
I can't take Liang Zidong's case.
You found Liang Zidong, right?
Right now, he'll only trust you.
And now you're dropping the case?
What is that supposed to mean?
It means...
First.
My focus is Mrs. Lin's case.
Have the firm issue me
an authorization letter immediately.
Second.
I decide my own career path from now on.
Shows, becoming an influencer, all that...
Don't waste my time with it.
Third.
Which cases I take or don't take,
and how I handle them,
are up to me.
Well, that's a new one.
Fine. I can live with that.
I'm fine with all of it.
But right now, I want to know
what exactly you said to Liang Zidong.
Answer me.
I'm actually curious about one thing.
When you saw Liang Zidong yesterday,
you two hadn't even met his family, right?
How'd you get the Representation Agreement
that got the Detective to let you in?
Because what I had
was actually a DUI case agreement.
Not Liang's Representation Agreement.
But I bet they wouldn't be interested
in checking those papers closely.
It's kind of like
marrying before getting the license.
Actually, through this case,
I've also seen my own limits.
Even if I can find someone through clues,
without you,
there's no way I could've
walked out of that hotel safely.
Enough.
It's Your time to shine.
Enjoy it.
If you really want me to take it,
fine.
But I want Zhao Yijie as my assistant.
Are you out of your mind?
I haven't been at Rujie long.
I don't have time to hire an assistant.
If I really have to do this,
then I'll have to handle
both Mrs. Lin's and Mr. Liang's cases.
I can't manage it all.
I
Hello
I heard you found Liang Zidong.
Yes.
He should be out soon.
So don't worry.
Then hurry up and get down to business.
We don't have much time left.
Okay.
What's wrong?
Zhao Yijie, oh, Zhao Yijie.
I finally realized something today.
You really treat this girl like a gem.
Or maybe...
She'll be the monster that devours us.
How does this...
Awu.
Math is very important.
You must do the math when you buy things.
Understand?
What's one plus nine?
Look, one.
Plus nine more.
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight, nine.
What does that equal?
It equals ten.
Write down ten.
One fried dough stick, one egg.
This five plus...
Five plus...
Three? Are you trying to say three?
This pen is out of ink.
Take out one with ink, okay?
What about nine minus six?
What is this?
Do you put just any junk in here?
It's a Gold nugget.
A Gold nugget?
Where did it come from?
Found it at Zhao Yijie's house.
These are his gold tooth and stones.
See how you want to handle them.
What are you looking at me for?
Work on your exercises for a bit.
Focus. Don't be careless.
I'm going to the restroom.
Can you draw a portrait for Grandpa?
Am I drawing you, Grandpa?
No, not me.
Draw someone else.
His face is rather square.
His eyes are a bit small and squinty.
Squinty eyes.
He has big bags under his eyes.
His ears are bigger than mine.